Good morning, the day before Nag Panchami is my
brother's fast. Today I am also fasting.
Let's get ready first, worship God
and then do all the other work.
I am fasting and she didn't want to have
breakfast either. So I just wanted to
make something for Manu, so
I made instant oats for her, which is healthy and just as good
.  I haven't been fasting at all for the past two years
because pregnancy,
delivery, and breastfeeding left
me with no energy to
fast, and even now,
I only fast very sparingly.   The first one was
Manu's video call with Nana in the afternoon, and these days
we all want to talk on video calls,
so we have video calls with Aaji, Baba, Nana, Maushi,
Mama Savi at least once a day. After that,
I went to
get the bell. My friend had already put it
away, so I
picked it up at her house and
started coming home after that.  Now she knows that I
buy a lot of trees, so she not only gave me this
crushed tree, but also this tree. When she
went to Anandi, I
also told her about this idol of Mahadev and that
I will pay for it because if God comes
home with a gift from someone, then it would be so much
trouble because if
we don't have a carry bag,
Pikuchi will cut it into 100 pieces.
Along with preparing the evening meal, I also made lahiyas here for Nagpunchami,
and these lahiyas turned out really well
and were ready in just an hour or two
.  Now,
if you have a daughter, you will
definitely relate that whenever there is a festival,
she would have to apply the mehendi before me
and even have it dried by her father.
I had applied the mehendi in a very simple way, but as soon as I did all that, it was
twelve o'clock and that was how the
day went. Let's go.